Guide to the Donald W. Baker College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection, 1950- 1969.
Baker, Donald W. College Veterinary Medicine Photograph Collection
- Myron Fincher and unidentified man at an Annual Conference, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00186)
  Description: Myron Fincher and unidentified man at an Annual Conference. The unidentified man is wearing a bow tie.
  Size and Number of Photographs:,
- Dr. Jack Geary and Mrs. Francis Fox, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00187)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Jack Geary and Mrs. Francis Fox
- Dr. John McAuliff, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00188)
  Description: Dr. John McAuliff standing on a boardwalk with his wife and another unidentified man.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "5"" x 7.5"" (cardboard) 9.5"" x 9"" (paper)", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Poppensiek greets the Donawicks at Commencement, 1963 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00189)
  Description: Dean Poppensiek greets W.J. Donawick and his wife at 1963 Commencement.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", "2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. and Mrs. John McAuliff (Box 1, Folder VPC.00190)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. John McAuliff on a boardwalk (only Dr. McAuliff in smaller picture)
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 9.5", 5.5" x 7.5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Henry E. Grossman and his wife, 1963 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00191)
  Description: Dr. Henry E. Grossman and his wife at 25th reunion of the class of 1938. See also VPC.00075, VPC.00147, VPC.00159, VPC.00477, and VPC.00478.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" 7.5"" x 9"" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Henry E. Grossman, 1964 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00192)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Henry E. Grossman, holding his wallet and a cigar. See also VPC.00182.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Roland Whitehead, K.H. Martin, Ed Martin and unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00193)
  Description: Roland Whitehead (class of 1944 ), K.H. Martin (Penn 1941), Ed Martin (class of 1967) and unidentified woman standing in a doorway.
- Dr. Fred Shigley, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00194)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Fred Shigley, MSU, 1923, and two unidentified men
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 1 print on cardboard
- Students examining soil, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00195)
  Description: 7 students examining soil with a stick in the field
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8"x 10", 1 print on cardboard, 1 transparency"
- Drs. Zepp, Baker, Hodges, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00196)
  Description: C. P. Zepp, Dewitt "Dutch" Baker, and Harry Hodges, and three unidentified men outside
  Size and Number of Photographs: "8"" x 10.5"" (cropped) 7.5"" x 11""", 2 prints on cardboard (one cropped)
- J. R. Hoyt, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00197)
  Description: J. R. Hoyt, class of 1916
- Group shot of Continuing Education group?, ca. 1960s (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00198)
  Description: Group shot of what appears to be a continuing education group. Visible squatting in the front row (3rd from left in white) is A. G. Danks. Visible in the first row standing (farthest left in white) is M. G. Fincher, Francis Fox and Steve Roberts are also
- James L. Hourrigan, 1961 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00199)
  Description: James L. Hourrigan, Kansas State University, class of 1940, senior staff veterinarian, ANH Epidemiologist, parasitologist, veterinarian, administrator
  Size and Number of Photographs: 10" x 7", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Dick Turk from Texas and unidentified man, 1959 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00200)
  Description: Candid of Dick Turk from Texas and unidentified man. Turk is wearing a hat and glasses.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9.5", 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 print on paper
- Dr. Westbrook and Dr. Arthur E. Scheld, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00201)
  Description: Dr. Westbrook and Dr. Arthur E. Scheld, Class of 1963, working on an animal organ (?). Westbrook is smoking a pipe
- James F. Shigley, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00202)
  Description: James F. Shigley, class of 1915
  Size and Number of Photographs: "6.5"" x 9.5"" 7"" x 14""", 3 prints on paper
- Honor Day 1954, 1954 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00203)
  Description: Honor Day 1954: Alfred Charles Steinhoff, Jr, James Paul Childress, Edward William Stewart, Herbert Tanzer, George Eugene Maurice, Robert Douglas Miller, Clyde Alton Corr, Henry Carroll Marsh, Robert William Dellers, Robert Stephen Stoll, John Ellis Wills
  Size and Number of Photographs: " 9"" x 6"" 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper
  Photographer (if other than Baker): Clayton Smith, Cornell Photo Science Service
- Drs. Lawrence Mott and William Oglesby, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00204)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Lawrence O. Mott, class of 1929, Kansas State Veterinary College and Dr. William T. Oglesby, class of 1931, Iowa State University Veterinary College. Mott is holding a pipe
  Size and Number of Photographs: "6.5"" x 9"" 7" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- R. R. Birch, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00205)
  Description: Candid of R. R. Birch
- Murray Jenkins, John Mettler and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00206)
  Description: Murray Jenkins, Class of 1946, John Mettler, Class of 1944, and unidentified man standing outside. There is a car in the background.
- Larry Conlon, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00207)
  Description: Candid of Larry Conlon, Class of 1923
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4.5" x 6", 1 print on cardboard
- L. E. Moore Jr., ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00208)
  Description: Candid of L. E Moore Jr. class of 1944, standing in the snow in front of one of the buildings of the old campus
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 11", 1 print on cardboard
- Ellis P. Leonard, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00209)
  Description: Candid of Ellis P. Leonard, Class of 1934
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7", 1 print on paper
- Dr. Van Houling, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00210)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Van Houling
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 2 prints on paper
- M. C. Tobin, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00211)
  Description: M. C Tobin of Denver Colorado
- J.O. Alberts, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00212)
  Description: J.O. Alberts, of the University of Illinois and graduate of U. Penn (1943), at the 75th Annual Meeting of the Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3" x 5" 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper
- Dr. Ray Meisels, 1958 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00213)
  Description: Candid of Raphael "Ray" Meisels, Class of 1934, smoking a pipe at 50th Annual Conference.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 10" x 10", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- James Noonan, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00214)
  Description: Candid of James Noonan, Class of 1958
- Roland Whitehead and Kenneth McEntee, 1955 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00215)
  Description: Candid of Roland G. Whitehead, class of 1944 and Kenneth McEntee, class of 1944, at the 47th Annual Conference.
  Size and Number of Photographs: Size; 7" x 8", 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. Frank Powell and family, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00216)
  Description: Dr. Frank Powell, class of 1963 and family
- David A Morrow, Class of 1960, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00217)
  Description: David A Morrow, Class of 1960, holding a camera in a lab.
- Charles Schroeder, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00218)
  Description: Candid of Charles Schroeder
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 5", 1 print on paper (color) 1 slide"
- Officers of the New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary, 1964 (Box 1, Folder VPC.00219)
  Description: Officers of the New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary. Left to Right: Mildred Fox, June Vaughn, Florence Grossman, and Marion Ford. Published in Ellis Leonard, "Veterinary Centennial in New York State," page 169.
- Unidentified veterinarians on a train, ca. 1950s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00220)
  Description: Unidentified veterinarians on a train. Man in first row has a pipe. See also. VPC.00137
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7", 10" x 10", 2 prints on paper (one cropped)
- Two unidentified men, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00221)
  Description: Two unidentified men sitting at a dining table, one smoking a cigarette with a coffee cup in front of him.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard (one cropped)
- Leonard Tyler and unidentified man, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00222)
  Description: Leonard Tyler (on left) and unidentified man. Tyler is being handed a briefcase with his initials on it.
- Drs. B.T. Simms and McKircher, ca. 1960s (Box 1, Folder VPC.00223)
  Description: Candid of B. T. Simms and D. G. McKircher of Davis California
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7"x 7.5", 1 print on paper
- Miss Halat, 1962 (Box 1 and 5a, Folder VPC.00224)
  Description: Candid of Miss Halat at a desk
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 3" x 5", 2 prints on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Clara Gage, April 1961 (Box 5a, Folder VPC.00225)
  Description: Candid of Clara Gage
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3.5" x 5", 1 print on paper
- Drs. Hugh Cameron and Chester A. Manthei, ca. 1960s (Box 2 and 5a, Folder VPC.00226)
  Description: Drs. Hugh Cameron, Class of 1931, and Chester A. Manthei (wearing hat and bow tie), MSU 1935. They are facing each other.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" (cropped) 8.5 x 11"" (cropped) 9" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard (cropped), 1 on paper"
- Circle of women on a lawn, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00227)
  Description: Circle of women on a lawn, including Ruth Baker
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6.5"x 4.5", 1 print on cardboard
- John Cheney, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00228)
  Description: Candid of John Cheney, class of 1924, pouring water into a tank on a truck
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 8", 6" x 8", 7.5" x 6", 3 prints on cardboard
- Dr. William P. Meleney, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00229)
  Description: Dr. William P Meleney, Class of 1951
- H.B. Risley and Denny Udall, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00230)
  Description: H. Brainard Risley, Class of 1931, and Denny Udall standing and talking
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 7", 1 print on paper
- William Sipple, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00231)
  Description: Candid of William Sipple, wearing a bow tie and holding a coffee cup.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 7", 1 print on particle board
- Sam Eddins, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00232)
  Description: Candid of Sam Eddins, class of 1938, standing at a microphone, wearing a plaid shirt.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5"x 9.5", 2 prints on paper
- Dr. Hoag, 1962 (Box 2 and 5a, Folder VPC.00233)
  Description: Warren Hoag, class of 1944, in a barn with cows.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 3" x 5", 3 prints on paper
- Drs. Hopkins, Steinfeldt, and Roberts, 1964 (Box 5a, Folder VPC.00234)
  Description: Left to Right: David Hopkins, Edward F. Steinfeldt, class of 1941, and Stephen J. Roberts at a New York State Veterinary College Alumni Association meeting. See also VPC.257 and VPC.00251.
  Size and Number of Photographs:, No prints
- Arthur E. Scheld, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00235)
  Description: Candid of Arthur E. Scheld, class of 1963, holding a dog.
- Drs. Kane, Baker, Hopson and Darrow, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00236)
  Description: Caption on reverse reads, "Judges at the County Fair." Pictured left to right are Joe Kane, Class of 1942, Dewitt "Dutch" Baker, Class of 1944, George Hopson, Class of 1928 and Darrow.
- Dr. Albert K. Tice and unidentified man, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00237)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Albert K. Tice, class of 1935, and unidentified man
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5"x 9.5", 7.5" x 9", 2 prints on cardboard
- Students collecting parasites, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00238)
  Description: 3 Students collecting parasites from a cow
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 7.5" x 9.5", 1 print on paper, 1 print on cardboard
- Pat Thomson Herr, Donald Swart and Dr. Kenny, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00239)
  Description: Patricia Thomson Herr, class of 1960, Donald A. Swart, class of 1960, and Dr. Kenny dissecting an animal.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5"x 7", 1 print on paper
- Louis P. Phaneuf, 1955 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00240)
  Description: Louis P. Phaneuf (Ph.D. 1957) holding a camera at the 47th Annual Conference
- Four men including Dr. Haley, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00241)
  Description: Four men including Dr. Haley, the State Veterinarian. Two are standing, two sitting. Haley is standing second from left.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 8", 1 print on paper
- Unidentified man and camel, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00242)
  Description: man holding a camel
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 10", 1 print on paper
- Veterinary buildings, exterior view, lower campus, ca. 1950 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00243)
  Description: Veterinary buildings, exterior view, lower campus. Tower Road looking East. Day Hall in the foreground.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9.5" x 7", 9.5" x 10.5", 2 prints on paper 1 transparency"
- Earl Sunderville and Charles Rife, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00244)
  Description: Earl Sunderville, Class of 1908, and Charles Rife, Class of 1925, standing and talking. Both are wearing bow ties.
- Drs. Nadler, Davis, and Goss, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00245)
  Description: Six men in a barn, possibly a continuing education class. Pictured are: Harold Nadler, class of 1939; Arthur E. Davis, class of 1944; and Allen Goss. Dr. Nadler is wearing a hat and standing in front two microscopes.
- Beth Sanderson, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00246)
  Description: Candid of Beth Sanderson. Husband was Charles Sanderson, class of 1953
- Douglas McBride and unidentified woman, 1955 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00247)
  Description: Douglas McBride, Class of 1955, and unidentified woman at graduation. He is wearing a graduation gown. Both are holding plates.
- Dr. and Mrs. Trevick from Jamaica, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00248)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. Trevick from Kingston, Jamaica
- 2 unidentified men and John Sickles, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00249)
  Description: Candid of 2 unidentified men (first may be Kenneth Benson) and John Sickles. Same event is pictured in VPC.00631
- Patricia Corwin Kubicki, ca. 1962 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00250)
  Description: Patricia Corwin Kubicki, class of 1963, with a small puppy
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- Drs. Hopkins, Steinfeldt, and Roberts, 1964 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00251)
  Description: Left to Right: David Hopkins, Edward F. Steinfeldt, class of 1941, and Stephen J. Roberts at a New York State Veterinary College Alumni Association meeting. See also VPC.234 and VPC.00257.
- R.W. Dougherty, 1955 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00252)
  Description: R.W. Dougherty, Oklahoma State University graduate. Class of 1936, at an Annual Conference. He is standing at a lectern, wearing a microphone and a name tag
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7" x 9", 1 print on paper
- Frank McClelland Jr. and Dr. and Mrs. Howe, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00253)
  Description: Candid of Frank McClelland Jr. and Dr. and Mrs. William M. "Mort" Howe, class of 1957, seated, laughing at a dinner party. Dr. Howe is holding a cigarette straight down between his fingers.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 9.5", 3" x 8", 3 prints on cardboard (one cropped)
- Dr. W. M. Howe and Mrs. Howe, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00254)
  Description: Dr. William M. Howe, class of 1957, and Mrs. Howe at a dinner table. Both are laughing. He has his hand to his chin. She is wearing long pearls.
- Drs. Hoppensted, Jenkins, W. S. Stone, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00255)
  Description: Candid of Drs. Hoppensted, Jenkins, W. S. Stone. Jenkins is wearing a patterned jacket and Stone is carrying a portfolio
- Arthur Gordon Danks, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00256)
  Description: Arthur Gordon Danks leaning forward, balancing on chairs.
- Drs. Hopkins, Steinfeldt, and Roberts, 1964 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00257)
  Description: Left to Right: David Hopkins, Edward F. Steinfeldt, class of 1941, and Stephen J. Roberts at a New York State Veterinary College Alumni Association meeting. See also VPC.00234 and VPC.00251
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10", 2 prints on paper 3 prints on cardboard"
- Dr. and Mrs. Jack Lowe, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00258)
  Description: Candid of Dr. and Mrs. Jack Lowe, Class of 1956, at a dinner table, presumably at a conference. He is wearing glasses, she is wearing a jumper.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 10" 9" x 9.5"", 1 print on paper 1 print on cardboard
- Dr. James A Baker and his wife, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00259)
  Description: Candid Dr. James A. Baker and his wife in front of car
  Size and Number of Photographs: 9" x 6", 1 print on cardboard
- Drs. Howe and Jeffers, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00260)
  Description: Candid of Mort Howe and Jeffers, both class of 1957. Both are wearing glasses and standing in a hallway of Schurman Hall.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Jack Tasker, Dr. Witter and two unidentified women at a picnic, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00261)
  Description: Jack Tasker, Dr. Witter and two unidentified women at a picnic. Witter is carrying a camera.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 6" x 9" 5" x 7", 1 print on paper (cropped), 1 print on cardboard
- William Meleney, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00262)
  Description: Candid of William P. Meleney, Class of 1951, in a garden with a dog between his legs
- Dr. Harold K. Cooper and unidentified woman, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00263)
  Description: Dr. Harold K. Cooper, class of 1938, and an unidentified woman each holding puppies
- Dr. Gillespie and Miss Newsom, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00264)
  Description: Dr. Gillespie and Margaret [Marion?] Newsom standing in front of a painting.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 4" x 7.5" (Newsom only), 2 prints on cardboard
- John Bentinck-Smith, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00265)
  Description: John Bentinck-Smith wearing an apron, holding a marking pencil and a beaker
- Miss Halat and Dr. Howard K Fuller, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00266)
  Description: Candid of Miss Halat and Dr. Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, sitting at a table reading stacks of papers (side angle).
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Miss Halat and Dr. Fuller, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00267)
  Description: Candid of Miss Halat and Dr. Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, sitting at a table reading stacks of papers (front angle).
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 2 prints on paper"
- Sam Eddins, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00268)
  Description: Candid of Sam Eddins, class of 1938, He is bent forward with a cigarette in his mouth and his wallet open in his hand.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 10" x 10", 1 print on paper (10 x 10) 1 print on cardboard (7.5 x 9.5)"
- Posed Group of NY Veterinarians, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00269)
  Description: Posed Group of NY Veterinarians in front of a mural. Seated, left to right: A.E. Merry, H.J. Milks, H.K. Miller, F.W. Andrews, R.S. MacKellar, Sr., A.L. Danforth, and E.B. Ackerman. Standing, left to right: L.A. Corwin, W.A. Hagan, L.J. Tillou, F.F. Fehr,
- Arthur Trayford and unidentified woman, 1961 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00270)
  Description: Candid of Arthur Trayford, class of 1927, and unidentified woman.
  Size and Number of Photographs: "3" x 5" 7" x 9", 2 prints on paper (1 cropped)
- Dr. Howard K. Fuller (Box 2, Folder VPC.00271)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Howard K. "Cap" Fuller, class of 1932, outside in summer.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 5" x 7" 8" x 10", 2 print on paper
- Mr. and Mrs. Layton, 1965 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00272)
  Description: Candid of Mr. and Mrs. Layton, the farrier. He is smoking a cigar. See also VPC.00374
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9" 3" x 5", 2 prints on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Robert McClellan, 1962 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00273)
  Description: Candid of Robert McClellan, class of 1934, in hat and coat indoors.
- Peter Olafson and W. S. Stone, 1965 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00274)
  Description: Candid of Peter Olafson and W. S. Stone and others seated at a banquet in a wallpapered room. Stone is laughing. Probably an Annual Conference. See also VPC.00294, VPC.00300, VPC.00301, VPC.00674 and VPC.00675.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" 3" x 5", 1 print on cardboard, 2 prints on paper (one cropped)"
- Dr. James D. Sweet, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00275)
  Description: Dr. James D. Sweet, class of 1932, holding a large winch of some sort, wearing coveralls and a bow tie.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 7.5" x 10.5", 2 prints on cardboard
- Earl S. Markham, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00276)
  Description: Earl S Markham, Class of 1912, at a conference, seated in a chair. See also VPC.00277 and VPC.00278.
- Earl S. Markham, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00277)
  Description: Earle S. Markham, Class of 1912, at an Annual Conference. See also VPC.00276 and VPC.00278.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8.5" x 9", 1 print on cardboard, 1 print on paper
- Earl S. Markham, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00278)
  Description: Earle S. Markham, Class of 1912, at an Annual Conference. See also VPC.00276 and VPC.00277.
- Dr. Norcrosse, unidentified man, and child, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00279)
  Description: Dr. Norcross, unidentified man, and child/ Child is wearing a snow suit.
  Size and Number of Photographs: 4" x 7", 5" x 7, 2 prints on paper
- Dr. Edwin Leonard, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00280)
  Description: Candid of Edwin Leonard, Class of 1940, and others at an exhibit for the New York State Veterinary Medical Society. The exhibit reads "Achievements of Veterinary Medicine"
- Dr. Aubrey Wooden and sheep, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00281)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Aubrey Wooden, class of 1923, with a sheep
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 11", 2 prints on paper
- William Evans and Thad Brown, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00282)
  Description: Candid of William Evans, class of 1932, and Thad Brown with 2 sheep
- Historical marker, ca. 1950s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00283)
  Description: Picture of a historical marker in DeRuyter, NY, the boyhood home of Ezra Cornell
- Dr. Myron Fincher and unidentified student, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00284)
  Description: Candid Dr. Myron Fincher and unidentified student, sitting at a dinner party table
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5", 3 prints on cardboard (one cropped)
- Dr. Herbert Gilman at his retirement, ca. June 1962 (Box 2, Folder VPC.00285)
  Description: Dr. Gilman at his retirement laughing and wearing lei
  Size and Number of Photographs: 3.5" x 5", 7" x 9", 2 prints on paper
- Dr. Louise Barr and unidentified woman, 1964 (Box 2 and 5b, Folder VPC.00286)
  Description: Candid of Dr. Louise Barr (holding glasses and wearing a corsage) and unidentified woman. See also VPC.00012
  Size and Number of Photographs: 7.5" x 9.5" (cardboard) 5"" x 7"" (paper) 3" x 5", "4 prints on cardboard (2 cropped) 2 prints on paper (1cropped)"
- Dr. Herr with two unidentified men and a sheep, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00287)
  Description: Dr. Herr with two unidentified men and a sheep
  Size and Number of Photographs: 8" x 7.5", 1 print on cardboard
- Mrs. Vaughn, ca. 1960s (Box 2, Folder VPC.00288)